Guide to the Andrea Callard Papers MSS.156
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Andrea Callard Artist Files
  - Subseries F: 1987-1989
    - Tenement Installation: program fragments, 1988; cuid22411 (Box 3, Folder 332)
    - Tenement Installation: essay, 1988; cuid22412 (Box 3, Folder 333)
    - Chintown Tenement Installation: historical photographs, 1988; cuid22413 (Box 3, Folder 334)
    - Chinatown tenement installation: black and white contact sheets documenting exhibition, 1988; cuid22414 (Box 3, Folder 335)
    - Chinatown tenement installation: black and white photographs documenting exhibition, 1988; cuid22415 (Box 3, Folder 336)
    - Chinatown tenement installation: Certificate of Appreciation from Chinatown History Project to Andrea Callard., 1988; cuid22416 (Box 3, Folder 337)
    - Chinatown tenement installation: press release, 1988; cuid22417 (Box 3, Folder 338)
    - Chinatown Tenement installation: press, 1988; cuid22418 (Box 3, Folder 339)
    - Prospect Park Boathouse Exhibit. Features Andrea Callar'ds "Branches", 1988; cuid22419 (Box 3, Folder 340)
    - Art Awareness Gallery. Group show featuring paintings by Andrea Callard, Installations by Susan Crowe, Elka Gould and Heidi Schlatter., 1988; cuid22420 (Box 3, Folder 341)
    - "Split Britches" produced and directed by Matthew Geller. Production, set and audio design by Andrea Callard., 1988; cuid22421 (Box 3, Folder 342)
    - Publicity postcards for DIA Art Foundation "If you lived here" exhibition organized by Martha Rosler. Features Andrea Callard and Sam Sue's "The Tenement: Place for Survival, Object of Reform" installation., 1989; cuid22422 (Box 3, Folder 343)
    - Publicity postcards for DIA "If you lived here" exhibition, altered in black marker to emphasize AC and SS's "The Tenement: Place for Survival, Object of Reform" installation.., 1989; cuid22423 (Box 3, Folder 344)
    - DIA "The Tenement" show, visitor register, 1989; cuid22424 (Box 3, Folder 346)
    - Notes and plans for DIA "The Tenement" installation, 1989; cuid22425 (Box 3, Folder 347)
    - DIA "The Tenement" installation program draft., 1989; cuid22426 (Box 3, Folder 348)
    - DIA "The Tenement" installation program, 1989; cuid22427 (Box 3, Folder 349)
    - DIA "The Tenement" borrowed material list, 1989; cuid22428 (Box 3, Folder 350)
    - DIA "The Tenement" installation paint chips, 1989; cuid22429 (Box 3, Folder 351)
    - DIA "The Tenement" installation slides., 1989; cuid22430 (Box 3, Folder 352)
    - DIA "The Tenement" installation black and white negatives, 1989; cuid22431 (Box 3, Folder 353)
    - DIA "If you livedhere" press release, includes statement on Andrea Callard and Sam Sue's "The Tenement", 1989; cuid22432 (Box 3, Folder 354)
    - Real Life Magazine article on DIA installation of "The Tenement: Place for Survival, Object of Reform", 1989; cuid22433 (Box 3, Folder 355)
    - Art in General "Abstract Places" group show., 1989; cuid22434 (Box 3, Folder 356)
    - Black and white contact sheets and negatives. Images of candid shots of kids, friends and tennis., 1989; cuid22435 (Box 3, Folder 357)
  - Subseries G: 1990-2000
    - Art in General window installation Andrea Callard's "Home Turf", 1990; cuid22436 (Box 3, Folder 358)
    - "Waste Stream Show" copies of photographs., 1990; cuid22437 (Box 3, Folder 361)
    - Earth Day Show at the Food Stamp Gallery. Includes work by Andrea Callard., 1990; cuid22438 (Box 3, Folder 362)
    - "From Receiver to Remote Control" at the New Museum of Contemporary Art. Curated by Matthew Geller, consulting by Andrea Callard. Invitation to a special reception., 1990; cuid22439 (Box 3, Folder 363)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. images of landfill., 1990; cuid22440 (Box 3, Folder 364)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of landfill., 1990; cuid22441 (Box 3, Folder 365)
    - Black and White contact sheet and negatives. Images of kids in costume., 1990; cuid22442 (Box 3, Folder 366)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Images of building demotition., 1990; cuid22443 (Box 3, Folder 367)
    - "The Return of the Cadavre Exquis" at the Drawing Center. Group show, includes Andrea Callard's work., 1993; cuid22444 (Box 3, Folder 368)
    - "Inside/Out" exhibit announcement. Bronx River Restoration project. Group show featuring Andrea Callard's work., 2000; cuid22445 (Box 3, Folder 369)
  - Subseries H: Art Education
    - Whistle Stop Daycare. Black and white contat sheets and negatives, 1976; cuid22446 (Box 4, Folder 370)
    - Whistle Stop Daycare. Color copy of photograph., ca. 1975-1976; cuid22447 (Box 4, Folder 371)
    - Bronx Museum of Arts. Eight color slides, event program and letter of recommendation., 1978; cuid22448 (Box 4, Folder 372)
    - Teaching-Malone file. includes letters from students, 53 color slides [grouped by AC], 1983; cuid22449 (Box 4, Folder 373)
    - Teaching-Malone file. 29 color slides and a Christmas card. [grouped by AC], 1983; cuid22450 (Box 4, Folder 374)
    - Hecksher. Letter and 12 color slides., 1983; cuid22451 (Box 4, Folder 375)
    - Black River file. Includes student letters, sketchbook, press clippings. [grouped by AC], 1983-1984; cuid22452 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - "Black River Residency" file. Press and 138 color slides., 1984 [grouped by AC]; cuid22453 (Box 4, Folder 377)
    - Rockland Center for the Arts. File contans press, contact information, school mailings, notes, planning letters etc., 1986-1987; cuid22454 (Box 4, Folder 378)
    - Rockland Center for the Arts Student Letters, 1986-1987; cuid22455 (Box 4, Folder 380)
    - Student "Love Letters" from Rockland students. Part 1, 1986-1987; cuid22456 (Box 4, Folder 381)
    - "Love Letters" from Rockland students. Part 2, 1986-1987; cuid22457 (Box 4, Folder 382)
    - Rockland Arts-in-Education Showcase. April 1, 1989, cuid22458 (Box 4, Folder 383)
    - New York State Summer School of the Arts. FIle includes black and white photographs, contact sheets and negatives as well as notes, contact information and promotional materials., 1990; cuid22459 (Box 4, Folder 384)
    - Paper-making workshop for Studio in a School., 1990; cuid22460 (Box 4, Folder 385)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of Andrea Callard with students., undated; cuid22461 (Box 4, Folder 387)
    - Lower East Side Printshop. Andrea Callard screenprinting materals demonstration., undated; cuid22462 (Box 4, Folder 388)
    - Notes and printed materials relating to pedagogical techniques., undated; cuid22463 (Box 4, Folder 389)
  - Subseries I: Miscellaneous materials
    - Notebook. includes sketches, lists, dreams and other writing., undated; cuid22464 (Box 4, Folder 390)
    - Notebook. Includes drawings, sketches and text., undated; cuid22465 (Box 4, Folder 391)
    - Notebook. Includes text and ink printing., undated; cuid22466 (Box 4, Folder 392)
    - Notebook. Includes text, inserts and sketches., undated; cuid22467 (Box 4, Folder 393)
    - Notebook. Includes text and sketches, undated; cuid22468 (Box 4, Folder 394)
    - Notebook. Includes text, sketches, letters., undated; cuid22469 (Box 4, Folder 395)
    - Notebook. Planning notes, some references to Colab. Includes inserts., undated; cuid22470 (Box 4, Folder 396)
    - Notebook. Includes drawings and stampings., undated; cuid22471 (Box 4, Folder 397)
    - Notebook. Includes ideas, lists, drawings and planning sketches., undated; cuid22472 (Box 4, Folder 398)
    - Notebook. Includes lists of expenses, pencil drawings and some text., undated; cuid22473 (Box 4, Folder 399)
    - Notebook. Includes sketches, watercolor and writing., undated; cuid22474 (Box 4, Folder 400)
    - Notebook. Notes,lists and planning sketches., undated; cuid22475 (Box 5, Folder 401)
    - Miscellaneous Press, undated; cuid22476 (Box 5, Folder 402)
    - Film Idea fragments, undated; cuid22477 (Box 5, Folder 406)
    - Video planning. informal "Video Proposal" outline., undated; cuid22478 (Box 5, Folder 407)
    - "Irrevocable Time", undated; cuid22479 (Box 5, Folder 408)
    - Life Spacing: An exercise. Notes and planning., undated; cuid22480 (Box 5, Folder 409)
    - Concentration Booth. Installation collaboration between Andrea Callard, Reese Williams and Winifred Carroll., undated; cuid22481 (Box 5, Folder 410)
    - "Fuck You Fashions", undated; cuid22482 (Box 5, Folder 411)
    - Household bug paintings., undated; cuid22483 (Box 5, Folder 412)
    - Doodlings and Balderdash notes. grouped by AC., undated; cuid22484 (Box 5, Folder 413)
    - Crayon and paint on white paper., undated; cuid22485 (Box 5, Folder 415)
    - Color printed pages. Includes "Musical Yellow Taxi", undated; cuid22486 (Box 5, Folder 416)
    - "Vidi View" diagram, undated; cuid22487 (Box 5, Folder 417)
    - Notecards. writing, pencil drawing, watercolor, collage, pen drawing. Grouped by AC., undated; cuid22488 (Box 5, Folder 418)
    - Filebox containing notecards. Content on cards includes writing, lists, drawings, collage and photographs. Miscellaneous dates. Grouped by AC., undated; cuid22489 (Box 9, Folder 419)
    - Drawings, grouped in envelope and labeled "Drawings", undated; cuid22490 (Box 5, Folder 421)
    - Rubbings, undated; cuid22491 (Box 5, Folder 422)
    - Broken toe print, undated; cuid22492 (Box 5, Folder 423)
    - "A Bridge from Memory, A Channel for Love", undated; cuid22493 (Box 5, Folder 424)
    - Label: "This green ladder functions...", undated; cuid22494 (Box 5, Folder 425)
    - Stickers of alphabet and numbers, undated; cuid22495 (Box 5, Folder 426)
    - "Double Lunar Dogs" written and directed by Joan Jonas. Sets and control panel by Andrea Callard., undated; cuid22496 (Box 5, Folder 427)
    - Andrea Callard drawing fo Spanner Paper Suit, undated; cuid22497 (Box 5, Folder 428)
    - Miscellaneous prints on paper., undated; cuid22498 (Box 5, Folder 429)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of a woman posing., undated; cuid22499 (Box 5, Folder 431)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of building exteriors and a mason jar., undated; cuid22500 (Box 5, Folder 432)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. "Statue" Reese Williams and Corine Stachner, undated; cuid22501 (Box 5, Folder 433)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Ed Chaplin "Confusciors", undated; cuid22502 (Box 5, Folder 434)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of rural and industrial buildings, trees., undated; cuid22503 (Box 5, Folder 435)
    - Black and white negatives and contact frame. Image of man at desk, shell and Clark buildings., undated; cuid22504 (Box 5, Folder 436)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of building demolition., undated; cuid22505 (Box 5, Folder 437)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Andrea Callard and Fred Krughoff., undated; cuid22506 (Box 5, Folder 438)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of Chicago and Andrea Callard's Father's second family., undated; cuid22507 (Box 5, Folder 439)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of Andrea Callard and Gary Brown., undated; cuid22508 (Box 5, Folder 440)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Images of Andrea Callard, Gary Brown and Berta Callard, undated; cuid22509 (Box 5, Folder 441)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of trees, Andrea Callard and friends, newspapers., undated; cuid22510 (Box 5, Folder 442)
    - Black and white cpntact sheet. Images of Andrea Callard's loft at 40 Lispenard and Fred Krughoff's loft on Water St. Undated but post 1976., cuid22511 (Box 5, Folder 443)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Images of Joshua Tree and 29 Palms with Baylor Trapnell., undated; cuid22512 (Box 5, Folder 444)
    - Black and white contact sheets and negatives. Images of kids and parking meters., undated; cuid22513 (Box 5, Folder 445)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of kids, pets, newspaper., undated; cuid22514 (Box 5, Folder 446)
    - Color photograph printed on white paper. Image of messy desk., undated; cuid22515 (Box 5, Folder 447)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of roots and kids., undated; cuid22516 (Box 5, Folder 448)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Images of Andrea Callard and young boy, probably her son., undated; cuid22517 (Box 5, Folder 449)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Images of kids, trees, chain and brickwork., undated; cuid22518 (Box 5, Folder 450)
    - Black and white negatives of New York., undated; cuid22519 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Black and white photographs, miscellaneous images., undated; cuid22520 (Box 5, Folder 452)
    - Black and white negative. Images of trees., undated; cuid22521 (Box 5, Folder 454)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of hands and feet., undated; cuid22522 (Box 5, Folder 455)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of Bangles and a woman standing., undated; cuid22523 (Box 5, Folder 456)
    - Miscellaneous color slides, unlabeled, undated; cuid22524 (Box 5, Folder 457)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of building exteriors and birds on a streetlight., undated; cuid22525 (Box 5, Folder 458)
    - Black and white copntact sheet and negatives. Images of car on George Washington Bridge and in parking lot., undated; cuid22526 (Box 5, Folder 459)
    - Black and white negatives and contact seets. Images of trees and buildings in winter., undated; cuid22527 (Box 5, Folder 460)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of construction site., undated; cuid22528 (Box 5, Folder 461)
    - Miscellaneous black and white photographs, undated; cuid22529 (Box 5, Folder 463)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of an unknown woman talking., undated; cuid22530 (Box 5, Folder 464)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of outside., undated; cuid22531 (Box 5, Folder 465)
    - Black and white black and white negatives, undated; cuid22532 (Box 5, Folder 466)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of satelite dish., undated; cuid22533 (Box 5, Folder 467)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of a party., undated; cuid22534 (Box 5, Folder 468)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of water, trees, trash., undated; cuid22535 (Box 5, Folder 469)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Images of Halloween, supper, toys., undated; cuid22536 (Box 5, Folder 470)
    - Misc. color negatives of horses and satelite dish, undated; cuid22537 (Box 5, Folder 471)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of trees and a house., undated; cuid22538 (Box 5, Folder 472)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet.Images of unknown woman at her computer., undated; cuid22539 (Box 5, Folder 473)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of garbage, park with child, playground., undated; cuid22540 (Box 5, Folder 474)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of trashcans., undated; cuid22541 (Box 5, Folder 475)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of building ornaments, undated; cuid22542 (Box 5, Folder 476)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of unknown man speaking., undated; cuid22543 (Box 5, Folder 477)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of outdoors., undated; cuid22544 (Box 5, Folder 478)
    - Color photo collage of roadtrip., undated; cuid22545 (Box 5, Folder 479)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets "Bride on the Bridge" photo collboration between Corine Schactner and Andrea Callard, undated; cuid22546 (Box 5, Folder 480)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of Bernice Rubin, Cara Perlman and Richard Friedman., undated; cuid22547 (Box 5, Folder 482)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of trashcans, bagpipes and kids., undated; cuid22548 (Box 5, Folder 483)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of trashcans and kids., undated; cuid22549 (Box 5, Folder 485)
    - Miscellaneous color negatives, undated; cuid22550 (Box 5, Folder 486)
    - Color negatives and snapshots. Documenting color and texture as, undated; cuid22551 (Box 5, Folder 487)
    - Color negatives. unlabeled. undated, cuid22552 (Box 5, Folder 488)
    - Black and white negatives. unlabeled. undated., cuid22553 (Box 5, Folder 489)
    - Color photographs printed on paper., undated; cuid22554 (Box 5, Folder 490)
    - Black and white negatives. Laurie Binder in Vermont., undated; cuid22555 (Box 5, Folder 491)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of Reese Williams with Brick and Megan at 40 Lispenard. Undated, post 1976, cuid22556 (Box 5, Folder 492)
    - Black and white contact sheets. Images of Andrea Callard, driving, snow and monuments., undated; cuid22557 (Box 5, Folder 493)
    - Black and white negatives. Documentation of drawings., undated; cuid22558 (Box 5, Folder 494)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of trees on Lispenard., undated; cuid22559 (Box 5, Folder 495)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of sculpture with branches, dog and woman., undated; cuid22560 (Box 5, Folder 496)
    - Black and white photograph of Dog [Brick?] outside black tent, indoors., undated; cuid22561 (Box 5, Folder 497)
    - Drawing, photograph and instructions grouped together in folder., undated; cuid22562 (Box 5, Folder 498)
- Series III: Administrative
  Series III: Administrative is divided into seven subseries. Subseries A includes grant proposals, calls for proposals, resumes and other materials relating to obtaining professional appointments and work. Subseries B includes paperwork regarding artworks loaned by Andrea Callard. Subseries C includes financial information such as receipts and taxes. Subseries D contains information regarding Andrea Callard's participation in organizations, for example her work with LINE. Subseries E contains employment information for student interns who worked with Andrea Callard. Subseries F includes paperwork relating to Andrea Callard's day to day work as an artist such as notes, lists and research copies. Finally, Subseries G includes artist photographs. Subseries arranged chronologically where possible, alphabetically in other instances.
  - Subseries A: Grants
    - Application to Cummington Community of the Arts, 1976; cuid22563 (Box 5, Folder 499)
    - Summary of Career Activity, 1976; cuid22564 (Box 5, Folder 500)
    - Resume, ca. 1979; cuid22565 (Box 5, Folder 501)
    - Public Art at the World Trade Center book, Call for submissions., 1980; cuid22566 (Box 5, Folder 502)
    - Notes on documents supplied with grant application, 1981; cuid22567 (Box 5, Folder 503)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts artist in residence program., 1982-1985; cuid22568 (Box 5, Folder 504)
    - Application materials for unknown art opportunity, 1983; cuid22569 (Box 5, Folder 505)
    - Public Art Fund, Bryant Park AIR residency application, 1983; cuid22570 (Box 5, Folder 506)
    - Art Park residency, 1983; cuid22571 (Box 5, Folder 507)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University file. Invitation to particiape in 1984-1985 Artist Forum., cuid22572 (Box 5, Folder 508)
    - Resume, ca 1985; cuid22573 (Box 5, Folder 510)
    - Cover letter and CV drafts, 1985; cuid22574 (Box 5, Folder 511)
    - Proposal for "Birds and Trowels" at the Anchorage, 1985; cuid22575 (Box 5, Folder 512)
    - Cityarts Workshop, 1985; cuid22576 (Box 5, Folder 513)
    - Art Matters, Inc. application for mural project., 1986; cuid22577 (Box 5, Folder 514)
    - "Neighborhood Climate" Application to New York State Council on the Arts Visual Artists Sponsored Projects., 1986; cuid22578 (Box 5, Folder 515)
    - Burchfield Art Center new works residency., 1986; cuid22579 (Box 5, Folder 516)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts artist in residency planning and oreintation workshop packet. Andrea Callard's Rockland residency., 1986; cuid22580 (Box 5, Folder 517)
    - Letter of inquiry to Rasnova/Laurie Yarotski Art Gallery, 1987; cuid22581 (Box 5, Folder 518)
    - Garden Projects, application and proposal for Harlem Rehabilitation Center, Hopkinson R and L Block Association and Good Neighbor Block Association., 1987; cuid22582 (Box 5, Folder 519)
    - Chicago Books, 1987; cuid22583 (Box 5, Folder 520)
    - Documentation to Municipal Arts Society regarding "The Tenement" installation at Chinatown History Project and DIA., 1989; cuid22584 (Box 5, Folder 521)
    - Anchor Foundation Incorporated application to Cultural Council FOundation., 1989; cuid22585 (Box 5, Folder 523)
    - Proposal for Rutgers Archives Printo Commission by Andrea Callard and Rand Russell., 1989; cuid22586 (Box 5, Folder 524)
    - Studio in a School Association, 1990; cuid22587 (Box 5, Folder 525)
    - Brendan Gill Prize information, undated; cuid22588 (Box 5, Folder 526)
  - Subseries B: Artwork loans
    - Insurance form, Custom and Culture part II, 1979; cuid22589 (Box 5, Folder 528)
    - MoMA "Committed to Print" show, Andrea Callard loaned Kiki Smith, Charlie Ahearn and Jane Dickson's "Cause/Effect" from Colab's street posters., 1990; cuid22590 (Box 5, Folder 529, Flat-file-folder 16)
  - Subseries C: Finances
    - Income Tax audit, 1973; cuid22591 (Box 5, Folder 530)
    - Motion Picture Laboratories Invoice, found in Media Box 4, 1976; cuid22592 (Box 5, Folder 531)
    - Receipt: Standard Adult Wheelchair, 1977; cuid22593 (Box 5, Folder 532)
    - "The Tenement" tax exempt paperwork, 1988; cuid22594 (Box 5, Folder 533)
    - "The Tenement" receipts, 1988; cuid22595 (Box 5, Folder 534)
    - "The Tenement" budget, 1988; cuid22596 (Box 5, Folder 535)
    - "The Tenement" at DIA, receipts, 1989; cuid22597 (Box 5, Folder 536)
    - Miscellaneous receipts, undated; cuid22598 (Box 5, Folder 537)
  - Subseries D: Organizational Participation
    - LINE Request For Proposals. LINE was a "service organization of artists that assists other artists with small grants for publication projects.", 1979; cuid22599 (Box 5, Folder 539)
    - Manhattan Decentralization panelist handbook, 1990; cuid22600 (Box 5, Folder 540)
    - Manhattan Decentralization Program recipient list., 1990; cuid22601 (Box 5, Folder 541)
    - Artists Call against US intervention in Central America, undated; cuid22602 (Box 5, Folder 542)
  - Subseries E: Interns
    - Ning, Stephan C., 1980-1989; cuid22603 (Box 5, Folder 543)
    - Rees, Sarah, 1987-1988; cuid22604 (Box 5, Folder 544)
  - Subseries F: Notes and Research copies
    - Ailanthus research copies, 1980; cuid22605 (Box 5, Folder 545)
    - Housing advocacy, 1989; cuid22606 (Box 5, Folder 546)
    - Recycling research copies, 1990; cuid22607 (Box 5, Folder 548)
    - Recycling research, 1990; cuid22608 (Box 5, Folder 549)
    - Miscellaneous notes and lists, undated; cuid22609 (Box 5, Folder 550)
    - Newspaper clipping "Wrist Camera Needs No Darkroom", undated; cuid22610 (Box 5, Folder 551)
    - page 25-26 of Neil Postman's Amusing Ourselves to Death., undated; cuid22611 (Box 5, Folder 552)
    - New Yorker cartoons, undated; cuid22612 (Box 5, Folder 553)
    - "The 'Youth Protest' and the 'Age of Creativity'" Pinchas Noy, undated; cuid22613 (Box 5, Folder 554)
    - Nature clippings, undated; cuid22614 (Box 5, Folder 555)
  - Subseries G: Artist Photographs
    - Fred Krughoff photographs of Andrea Callard. Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Late 1970s, ca. 1978; cuid22615 (Box 6, Folder 556)
    - Callard portraits by Teri Slotkin prior to Malone Residency. Black and white contact sheets, three color slides, 1982; cuid22616 (Box 6, Folder 557)
    - Peter Bellamy portraits of Andrea Callard. Used for her profile in "The Artist Book". Black and white contact sheets., 1983; cuid22617 (Box 6, Folder 558)
    - Unknown photographer, portraits of Andrea Callard. Black and white negatives and contact sheet, undated; cuid22618 (Box 6, Folder 559)